A Guide to the Beall Booth Family Papers, 1751-1932
Colonial Williamsburg Foundation
- Personal Papers, 1751-1932, 1 box (Box-folder 110:1-11)
  - Family Photographs, Undated, 1 Folder (3 Photographs) (Box-folder 110:11)
    Photographs of the Beall-Booth family in Kentucky. The images contain family members from Norborne Booth Beall and his childern to Galt Worthington Booth and his children.
    - Undated (Box-folder 110:11)
    - Undated (Box-folder 110:11)
    - Undated (Box-folder 110:11)